Some doors should never be opened.
The Pact is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Nicholas McCarthy.
After their mother passes away, sisters Nicole and Annie reluctantly
return to their childhood home to pay their last respects.
While staying overnight in the house, the sisters sense a mysterious presence in their midst: noises startling them
in the night, objects moving about, a fallen picture of an unknown woman posed next to their mother.
Annie begins experiencing a series of intense and disturbing dreams - visions that lead her to
uncover something terrible about her mother's past that is finally revealing itself.
Annie Barlow, played by Caity Lotz.
Bill Creek, played by Casper Van Dien.
Nichole, played by Agnes Bruckner.
Stevie, played by Haley Hudson.
Eva, played by Dakota Bright.
Giles, played by Sam Ball.
The Pact is a 2012 American supernatural horror film written and directed by
Nicholas McCarthy and starring Caity Lotz and Casper Van Dien.
The film was made following the success of McCarthy's short film of the
same name which showed at the 2011 Sundance Film Festival.
The film follows Annie, whose mother has recently died, as she tries to discover
what caused her sister Nicole and her cousin Liz to disappear.
The film explores themes of haunting, childhood home, death of mother, mourning.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and emotional.